Abbey Theatre collection, 1921-1995
Emory University
- Programs, 1921-1995 (bulk 1925-1942), Series 2; Box 2 - Box 8: folders 1-30
  - 1932 August 1, 5: O'CASEY, Sean, The Plough and the Stars (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - 1932 August 2, 4, 6: YEATS, W.B., The Words Upon the Window Payne; MURRAY, T.C., Birthright; LADY GREGORY, The Workhouse Ward (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - 1932 August 9 and 11: YEATS, W.B., Cathleen Ni Houlihan (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - 1932 August 10, 12, 13: SYNGE, J.M., In the Shadow of the Glen; ROBINSON, Lennox, The Whiteheaded Boy (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - 1932 August 23 and 25: ERVINE, St. John, John Ferguson (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - 1932 August 24, 26, 27: O'CASEY, Sean, The Shadow of a Gunman; ROBINSON, Lennox, Crabbed Youth and Age (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - 1932 August 29 and following nights: MacNAMARA, Brinsley, Look At the Heffernans! (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - 1932 September 6 and following nights: CARROLL, Paul Vincent, Things That Are Caesar's (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - 1932 September 20 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, The Rig House (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - 1932 September 26 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, The Far-Off Hills (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - 1933 April 15 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, Drama at Irish (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - 1933 July 31 and following nights: MURRAY, T.C., Michaelmas Eve (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - 1933 August 14 and following nights: MURRAY, T.C., The Pine in the Fields; SYNGE, J.M., The Playboy of the Western World (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - 1933 August 28 and following nights: CARROLL, Paul Vincent, Things That Are Caesar's (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - 1933 September 4 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Mountain Dew (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - 1933 September 11 and following nights: MacNAMARA, Brinsley, Margaret Gillan (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - 1933 September 18 and following nights: O'CASEY, Sean, The Plough and the Stars (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - 1933 September 25 and following nights: O'LEARY, Frank X, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - 1933 October 2 and following nights: MacNAMARA, Brinsley, Look at the Heffernans! (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - 1933 October 9 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Paul Twyning (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - 1933 October 16 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, Drama at Inish or Is Life Worth Living?: By permission of Sydney W. Carroll (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - 1933 October 23 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, Drama at Inish or Is Life Worth Living?: By permission of Sydney W. Carroll (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - 1933 October 30 and following nights: YEATS, W.B., The Words Upon the Window Payne; McNULTY, Edward, The Courting of Mary Doyle (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - 1933 November 6 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, The Whiteheaded Boy; LADY GREGORY, The Rising of the Moon (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - 1933 November 20 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Grogan and the Ferret (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - 1933 November 27 and following nights: SOPHOCLES: Oedipus the King: Prose version by W.B. Yeats; MURRAY, T.C., Sovereign Love (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - 1933 December 4, 5, 6: ERVINE, St. John, John Ferguson (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - 1933 December 11 and following nights: SHIELS, George, The New Gossoon (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - 1933 December 18-22: ROBINSON, Lennox, Never the Time and the Place; McNULTY, Edward, The Lord Mayor (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - [1933?]: SHIELS, George, Professor Tim (contains sketch of "Ballydonal House") (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - [1933?]: MacNAMARA, Brinsley, The Glorious Uncertainty (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - 1934 January 4 and following nights: SHAW, George Bernard, You Never Can Tell (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - 1934 January 8 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Professor Tim (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - 1934 January 15 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, The Far-Off Hills (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - 1934 January 22 and following nights: TOCHER, E.W., The Moon in the Yellow River (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - 1934 January 29 and following nights: LADY GREGORY, Spreading the News; O'CASEY, Sean, The Shadow of a Gunman (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - 1934 Feb 5 and following nights: POWER, Arthur, The Marriage Packet (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - 1934 Feb 12 and following nights: MAYNE, Rutherford, Peter (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - 1934 March 31, April 2 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Grogan and the Ferret (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - 1934 April 9 and following nights: O'CASEY, Sean, Juno and the "Paycock" (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - 1934 April 23 and following nights: O'NEILL, Eugene, Days Without End (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - 1934 April 30 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, Drama at Inish or Is Life Worth Living? By permission of Sydney W. Carroll (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - 1934 May 7 and following nights: MacNAMARA, Brinsley, Look at the Heffernans! (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - 1934 May 14 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Mountain Dew (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - 1934 May 28 and following nights: O'CASEY, Sean, The Plough and the Stars (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - 1934 June 4 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Paul Twyning (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - 1934 June 11, 12, 13: LADY GREGORY,,The Rising of the Moon; McNULTY, Edward, The Lord Mayor (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - 1934 June 14, 15, 16: MacNAMARA, Brinsley, The Glorious Uncertainty (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - 1934 June 26 and following nights: MAYNE, Rutherford, Bridgehead (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - 1934 July 2 and following nights: SHIELS, George, The New Gossoon (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - 1934 July 16 and following nights: SYNGE, J.M., In the Shadow of the Glen; McNULTY, Edward, The Courting of Mary Doyle (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - 1934 July 24 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, All's over, Then? (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - 1934 July 30 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, Church Street; YEATS, W.B., The Resurrection; YEATS, W.B., The King of the Great Clock Tower (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - 1934 August 6, 8, 10: SHIELS, George, Grogan and the Ferret (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - 1934 August 7, 9, 11: O'CASEY, Sean, Juno and the "Paycock" (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - 1934 August 13 and following nights: O'NEILL, Eugene, Days Without End (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - 1934 August 20, 21, 22: ROBINSON, Lennox, The Far-Off Hills (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - 1934 August 23, 24, 25: LADY GREGORY, Spreading the News; SYNGE, J.M., The Playboy of the Western World (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - 1934 August 28 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, Drama at Inish or Is Life Worth Living?: By permission of Sydney W. Carroll (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - 1934 September 3 and following nights: O'CASEY, Sean, The Plough and the Stars (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - 1934 September 10 and following nights: SYNGE, J.M., The Well of the Saints; LADY GREGORY, Hyacinth Halvey (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - 1934 September 20, 21, 22: SYNGE, J.M., Riders to the Sea; McNULTY, Edward, The Lord Mayor (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - 1934 October 1 and following nights: FEARON, W.R., Parnell of Avondale (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - 1934 October 8 and following nights: FEARON, W.R., Parnell of Avondale (contains inserted announcement by Lennox Robinson) (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - 1934 October 25 and following nights: SHAKESPEARE, William, Macbeth (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - 1934 November 20 and following nights: SCHNITZLER, Arthur, Gallant Cassian (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - 1934 December 3 and following nights: PIRANDELLO, Luigi, Six Characters in Search of an Author (contains insert announcing a play to follow and introduction by Lennox Robinson) (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - 1934 December 10 and following nights: LORD DUNSANY, The Glittering Gate; LADY GREGORY, The Canavians (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - 1934 December 26 and following nights: MUNRO, C.K., At Mrs. Beam's (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - 1935 April 20 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, Drama at Inish or Is Life Worth Living? (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 1935 May 6 and following nights: O'KELLY, Seumas, The Parnellite (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 1935 August 5, 6, 7: MAYNE, Rutherford, Bridgehead (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 1935 August 8, 9, 10: O'CASEY, Sean, The Plough and the Stars (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 1935 August 12 and following nights: O'CASEY, Sean, The Silver Tassie (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 1935 August 19 and following nights: SHAW, George Bernard, John Bull's Other Island (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 1935 August 26 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Grogan and the Ferret (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - 1935 September 2 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, The Far-Off Hills (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - 1935 September 23 and following nights: SHIELS, George, The New Gossoon (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - 1935 October 14 and following nights: FEARON, W.R., Parnell of Avondale (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - 1935 October 21 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, Drama at Inish or Is Life Worth Living? (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - 1935 October 28 and following nights: O'CASEY, Sean, Juno and the "Paycock" (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - 1935 November 4 and following nights: OBEY, Andre, Noah: Translated by Arthur Wilmurt (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - 1935 November 18 and following nights: OBEY, Andre, Noah: Translated by Arthur Wilmurt (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - 1935 November 25 and following nights: MacNAMARA, Brinsley, The Glorious Uncertainty (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - 1935 December 2 and following nights: PENAM, Jose Maria, A Saint in a Hurry: Translated by Hugh De Blacam (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - 1935 December 9 and following nights: MOLLOY, Maura, Summer's Day (contains an announcement) (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - 1935 December 16 and following nights: YEATS, W.B., The Words Upon the Window Payne; O'CASEY, Sean, The Shadow of a Gunman (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - 1935 December 29: LADY GREGORY, The Rising of the Moon; YEATS, W.B., The Land of Heart's Desire; O'KELLY, Seumas, Meadowsweet (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - 1935 December 26 and following nights: SHERIDAN, Richard Brinsley, The Critic or A Tragedy Rehearsed: Modernised by Lennox Robinson (contains introduction by Lennox Robinson) (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - 1936 January 6 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Professor Tim (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - 1936 January 22 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Paul Twyning (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - 1936 January 27 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Paul Twyning (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - 1936 Feb 3 and following nights: MacNAMARA, Brinsley, The Grand House in the City (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - 1936 Feb 10 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Mountain Dew (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - 1936 Feb 17 and following nights: O'CASEY, Sean, The Plough and the Stars (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - 1936 March 2 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, The Far-Off Hills (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - 1936 March 9 and following nights: MURRAY, T.C., Autumn Fire (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - 1936 March 16 and following nights: DEEVY, Teresa, Katie Roche (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - 1936 March 23 and following nights: MacNAMARA, Brinsley, Look at the Heffernans! (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - 1936 March 30 and following nights: MAYNE, Rutherford, Bridgehead (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - 1936 April 20 and following nights: MacNAMARA, Brinsley, The Grand House in the City (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - 1936 April 27 and following nights: ERVINE, St. John, Boyd's Shop (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - 1936 May 4 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Grogan and the Ferret (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - 1936 May 11 and following nights: JOHNSTON, Denis, The Moon in the Yellow River (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - 1936 May 18 and following nights: YEATS, W.B., The Shadowy Waters; O'CASEY, Sean, The Shadow of a Gunman (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - 1936 May 25 and following nights: SHIELS, George, The New Gossoon (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - 1936 June 1 and following nights: FLECKER, James Elroy, Hassan: Incidental music by Frederick Delius (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - 1936 July 13 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, Drama at Inish or Is Life Worth Living? (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - 1936 July 20 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, Drama at Inish or Is Life Worth Living? (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - 1936 July 27 and following nights: DEEVY, Teresa, The King of Spain's Daughter; SYNGE, J.M., The Playboy of the Western World (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - 1936 August 3, 5, 7: ROBINSON, Lennox, The Far-Off Hills (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - 1936 August 4, 6, 8: COLUM, Padraic, Thomas Muskerry; O'KELLY, Seumas, Meadowsweet (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - 1936 August 10 and following nights: DEEVY, Teresa, The King of Spain's Daughter; YEATS, W.B., Deirdre, O'KELLY, Seumas, Meadowsweet (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - 1936 August 17 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Professor Tim (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - 1936 August 24 and following nights: MOLLOY, Maura, Summer's Day; LADY GREGORY, The Rising of the Moon (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - 1936 August 31 and following nights: LORD DUNSANY, The Glittering Gate; SYNGE, J.M., The Playboy of the Western World (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - 1936 September 7 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, The Far-Off Hills (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - 1936 September 14 and following nights: O'DALY, Cormac, The Silver Jubilee; O'RIORDAN, Conal, The Piper (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - 1936 September 21 and following nights: O'CASEY, Sean, The Plough and the Stars (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - 1936 September 28 and following nights: ERVINE, St. John, Boyd's Shop (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - 1936 October 5 and following nights: YEATS, W.B., Kathleen Ni Houlihan; O'CASEY, Sean, The Shadow of a Gunman (contains marginalia on back page) (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - 1936 October 19 and following nights: SHIELS, George, The Jailbird (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - 1936 October 26 and following nights: SHIELS, George, The Passing Day (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - 1936 November 2 and following nights: LADY GREGORY, Hyacinth Halvey; SHAW, George Bernard, Fanny's First Play (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - 1936 November 9 and following nights: DEEVY, Teresa, The Wild Goose (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - 1936 November 16 and following nights: O'CASEY, Sean, Juno and the "Paycock" (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - 1936 November 23 and following nights: SHIELS, George, The New Gossoon (contains introduction regarding upcoming play by Lennox Robinson) (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - 1936 November 30 and following nights: O'CALLAGHAN, Maeve, Wind from the West (contains introduction by Lennox Robinson) (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - 1936 December 7 and following nights: O'CALLAGHAN, Maeve, Wind from the West: (contains introduction by Lennox Robinson and advertising insert from Cavendish Furniture Co., Ltd.) (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - 1936 December 14 and following nights: SHIELS, George, The Jailbird (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - 1937 January 11 and following nights: TOLLER, Ernst and JOHNSTON, Denis, Blind Man's Buff (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 1937 January 18 and following nights: TOLLER, Ernst and JOHNSTON, Denis, Blind Man's Buff (contains introduction regarding an upcoming play by Frank O'Connor) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 1937 January 25 and following nights: CARROLL, Paul Vincent, Shadow and Substance (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 1937 Feb 1 and following nights: YEATS, W.B., STEPHENS, James, and HIGGINS, F.R., Songs and Poems; DEEVY, Teresa, Katie Roche (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 1937 Feb 8 and following nights: O'DALY, Cormac, The Silver Jubilee; O'CASEY, Sean, The End of the Beginning (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 1937 Feb 15 and following nights: MacNAMARA, Brinsley, Margaret Gillan (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 1937 Feb 22 and following nights: FANNING, A.P., Vigil; SHAW, George Bernard, Arms and the Man (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - 1937 March 1 and following nights: O'CASEY, Sean, The Plough and the Stars (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - 1937 March 8 and following nights: MacNAMARA, Brinsley, Look at the Heffernans? (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - 1937 March 15 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, Drama at Inish or Is Life Worth Living? (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - 1937 April 12 and following nights: SHIELS, George, "Quin's Secret"(contains introduction regarding upcoming play) (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - 1937 April 19 and following nights: LADY GREGORY, Dervorgilla; ROBINSON, Lennox, Killycreggs in Twilight (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - 1937 April 26 and following nights: SHIELS, George, The Jailbirds (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - 1937 May 3, 4, 5: ERVINE, St. John, Boyd's Shop (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - 1937 May 6, 7, 8: CARROLL, Paul Vincent, Shadow and Substance (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - 1937 May 10 and following nights: O'CASEY, Sean, Juno and the "Paycock": (contains introduction regarding upcoming play) (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - 1937 May 24 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Grogan and the Ferret (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - 1937 July 12 and following nights: TOLLER, Ernst and JOHNSTON, Denis, Blind Man's Buff (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - 1937 July 19 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, The Far-Off Hills (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - 1937 July 26 and following nights: SHIELS, George, The New Gossoon (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - 1937 August 9 and following nights: O'CALLAGHAN, Maeve, The Patriot (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - 1937 August 16 and following nights: LADY GREGORY, The Rising of the Moon; SYNGE, J.M., The Playboy of the Western World (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - 1937 August 23 and following nights: MURRAY, T.C., Spring; DEEVY, Teresa, Temporal Powers (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - 1937 September 6 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, The Lost Leader (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - 1937 September 13 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Quin's Secret (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - 1937 September 20 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, Drama at Inish or Is Life Worth Living? (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - 1937 September 27 and following nights: D'ALTON, Louis, The Man in the Cloak (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - 1937 October 4 and following nights: D'ALTON, Louis, The Man in the Cloak (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - 1937 October 11 and following nights: ERVINE, St. John, Boyd's Shop (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - 1937 October 25 and following nights: HUNT, Hugh and O'CONNOR, Frank, The Invincible (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - 1937 November 1 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, The Far-Off Hills (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - 1937 November 8 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Cartney and Kevney (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - 1937 November 15 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Cartney and Kevney (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - 1937 November 22 and following nights: CARROLL, Paul V., Coggerers; SYNGE, J.M., The Playboy of the Western World (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - 1937 November 29 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, The Whiteheaded Boy (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - 1938 January 3 and following nights: O'FAOLAIN, Sean, She Had to do Something: (contains actor replacement notice) (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - 1938 January 10 and following nights: SHIELS, George, The New Gossoon (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - 1938 January 24 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Neal Maquade (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - 1938 January 31 and following nights: HUNT, Hugh and O'CONNOR, Frank, The Invincibles (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - 1938 Feb 7 and following nights: ERVINE, St. John, Boyd's Shop (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - 1938 Feb 14 and following nights: MURRAY, T.C., A Spot in the Sun (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - 1938 Feb 21 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, Drama at Inish or Is Life Worth Living? (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - 1938 Feb 28 and following nights: HUNT, Hugh and O'CONNOR, Frank, Moses' Rock (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - 1938 March 7 and following nights: HUNT, Hugh and O'CONNOR, Frank, Moses' Rock (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - 1938 March 21 and following nights: TOLLER, Ernst and JOHNSTON, Denis,,Blind Man's Buff (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - 1938 March 28 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Quin's Secret (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - 1938 April 4 and following nights: LADY GREGORY, The Rising of the Moon; YEATS, W.B., On Baile's Strand; GANLY, Andrew, The Dear Queen (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - 1938 April 18 and following nights: O'CASEY, Sean, The Plough and the Stars (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - 1938 April 25 and following nights: O'CASEY, Sean, The Plough and the Stars (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - 1938 May 2 and following nights: SHIELS, George, The New Gossoon (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - 1938 May 16 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, The Far-Off Hills (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - 1938 May 23 and following nights: SYNGE, J.M., Riders to the Sea; SYNGE, J.M., The Well of the Saints (contains announcement regarding a benefit performance) (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - 1938 July 11 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, Church Street; LADY GREGORY, Damer's Gold (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - 1938 July 18 and following nights: MURRAY, T.C., Maurice Harte; SHAW, George Bernard, The Shewing-Up of Blanco Posnet (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - 1938 July 25 and following nights: JOHNSTON, Denis, The Moon in the Yellow River (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - 1938 August 1, 2, 3: CARROLL, Paul Vincent, Shadow and Substance (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - 1938 August 4, 5, 6: HUNT, Hugh and O'CONNOR, Frank, The Invincibles (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - 1938 August 22 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, Drama at Inish or Is Life Worth Living? (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - 1938 September 19 and following nights: FOLEY, Charles, The Great Adventure; ROBINSON, Lennox, Bird's Nest (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - 1938 September 26 and following nights: TOLLER, Ernst and JOHNSTON, Denis, Blind Man's Buff (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - 1938 October 3 and following nights: SHIELS, George, The Jailbird (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - 1938 October 10 and following nights: RYNEE, Mary, Pilgrims (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - 1938 October 17 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, The Far-Off Hills (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - 1938 October 24 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Quin's Secret (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - 1938 October 31 and following nights: O'CASEY, Sean, Juno and the "Paycock": (contains insert from Gaiety Theatre) (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - 1938 November 7 and following nights: LADY GREGORY, The Gaol Gate (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - 1938 November 14 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Professor Tim (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - 1938 November 21 and following nights: ERVINE, St. John, Boyd's Shop (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - 1938 November 28 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Grogan and the Ferret (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - 1938 December 5 and following nights: YEATS, W.B., Purgatory; SYNGE, J.M., The Playboy of the Western World (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - 1938 December 12 and following nights: O'CASEY, Sean, The Shadow of a Gunman; De BHILMOT, Seamus, Baintighearna an Ghorta (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - 1938 December 26 and following nights: O'CONNOR, Frank, Time's Pocket (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - 1939 January 2 and following nights: O'CASEY, Sean, The Plough and the Stars (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 1939 January 9 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Paul Twyning (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 1939 January 16 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Paul Twyning (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 1939 January 23 and following nights: SHIELS, George, The Jailbird (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - 1939 Feb 6 and following nights: SYNGE, J.M., In the Shadow of the Glen (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 1939 Feb 13 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, Drama at Inish or Is Life Worth Living? (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - 1939 Feb 20 and following nights: SHIELS, George, The New Gossoon (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - 1939 Feb 27 and following nights: TOLLER, Ernst and JOHNSTON, Denis, Blind Man's Buff (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - 1939 March 6 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Professor Tim (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - 1939 March 20 and following nights: WALTON, Louis, To-Morrow Never Comes (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - 1939 March 27 and following nights: ERVINE, St. John, Mixed Marriage; SHAW, George Bernard, Village Wooing (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - 1939 April 3, 4, 5, 6: LADY GREGORY, The Story Brought by Bright (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - 1939 April 17 and following nights: MONTGOMERY, J.K, The Heritage (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - 1939 April 24 and following nights: GANLY, Andrew, The Dear Queen; ROBINSON, Lennox, Bird's Nest (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - 1939 May 1 and following nights: CARROLL, Paul V, Shadow and Substance (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - 1939 May 8 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Insurance Money; ROBINSON, Lennox, Never the Time and the Place (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - 1939 May 22 and following nights: O'CASEY, Sean, Juno and the "Paycock" (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - 1939 May 29 and following nights: O'DALY, Cormac, The Silver Jubilee (Box 7, Folder 18)